blogcarnival.com 2010-11-20

# Blog Carnival - Privacy Policy

This is the privacy policy for Blog Carnival LLC, which are a part of our Terms of Service. Our homepage on the Web is located at [ http://blogcarnival.com](http://blogcarnival.com/). The full text of our privacy policy is available on the Web at [ http://blogcarnival.com/bc/p_policy.html](http://blogcarnival.com/bc/p_policy.html). 

We invite you to contact us if you have questions about this policy. You may contact us by mail at the following address:

    Blog Carnival, LLC
    101 S. Rainbow #28-24
    Las Vegas, NV  89145
    US

## Dispute Resolution and Privacy Seals

We have the following privacy seals and/or dispute resolution mechanisms. If you think we have not followed our privacy policy in some way, they can help you resolve your concern. 

  * **Contact Us** : Please [contact us](http://blogcarnival.com/bc/oprof.php?id=1) if you have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy policy. 

## Additional Information

This policy may be updated from time to time, at our discretion. 

## Data Collection

P3P policies declare the data they collect in groups (also referred to as "statements"). This policy contains 2 data groups. The data practices of each group will be explained separately. 

* * *

### Group "Basic information"

We collect the following information: 

  * Click-stream data
  * HTTP protocol elements
  * Search terms

This data will be used for the following purposes:

  * Completion and support of the current activity.
  * Web site and system administration.
  * Research and development.

This data will be used by ourselves and our agents. 

The following explanation is provided for why this data is collected:

> Data collected from all Web users: access logs, and search strings (if entered).

* * *

### Group "Cookies"

At the user's option, we will collect the following data: 

  * HTTP cookies

This data will be used for the following purposes:

  * Research and development.
  * One-time tailoring.

This data will be used by ourselves and our agents. 

The following explanation is provided for why this data is collected:

> Cookies are used to track visitors to our site, so we can better understand what portions of our site best serve you.

* * *

## Cookies

Cookies are a technology which can be used to provide you with tailored information from a Web site. A cookie is an element of data that a Web site can send to your browser, which may then store it on your system. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it. 

Our site makes use of cookies. Cookies are used for the following purposes: 

  * User targeting 
  * Research and development 

* * *

## Compact Policy Summary

The compact policy which corresponds to this policy is: 

        CP="NOI DSP CURa ADMa DEVa TAIa OUR BUS IND UNI COM NAV INT"

The following table explains the meaning of each field in the compact policy. 

**Field**|  **Meaning**  
---|---  
`CP=` | This is the compact policy header; it indicates that what follows is a P3P compact policy.  
`NOI` |  No identifiable information is collected, so no access is possible.   
`DSP` |  The policy contains at least one dispute-resolution mechanism.   
`CURa` |  The data is used for completion of the current activity.   
`ADMa` |  The data is used for site administration.   
`DEVa` |  The data is used for research and development.   
`TAIa` |  The data is used for tailoring the site.   
`OUR` |  The data is given to ourselves and our agents.   
`BUS` |  Our business practices specify how long the data will be kept.   
`IND` |  The data will be kept indefinitely.   
`UNI` |  Unique identifiers are collected.   
`COM` |  Computer information is collected.   
`NAV` |  Navigation and clickstream data is collected.   
`INT` |  Interactive data is collected.   
  
The compact policy is sent by the Web server along with the cookies it describes. For more information, see the P3P deployment guide at <http://www.w3.org/TR/p3pdeployment>. 

* * *

## Policy Evaluation

Microsoft Internet Explorer 6 will evaluate this policy's compact policy whenever it is used with a cookie. The actions IE will take depend on what privacy level the user has selected in their browser (Low, Medium, Medium High, or High; the default is Medium. In addition, IE will examine whether the cookie's policy is considered satisfactory or unsatisfactory, whether the cookie is a session cookie or a persistent cookie, and whether the cookie is used in a first-party or third-party context. This section will attempt to evaluate this policy's compact policy against Microsoft's stated behavior for IE6. 

**Note:** this evaluation is currently experimental and should not be considered a substitute for testing with a real Web browser. 

**Satisfactory policy** : this compact policy is considered _satisfactory_ according to the rules defined by Internet Explorer 6. IE6 will accept cookies accompanied by this policy under the High, Medium High, Medium, Low, and Accept All Cookies settings.   

* * *

Last updated: 1/21/2008
